{"data":[{"question":"He arrived ______ the meeting just in time.","a":"in","b":"on","c":"-","d":"at","answer":"4","explain":"\n\n- Arrive in : general location\n\n- Arrive at: specific location\n\n","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"72","subcategorylv2":"4","type":"1"},{"question":"The plane arrived ______ Majorca twelve hours late.","a":"-","b":"in","c":"on","d":"at","answer":"2","explain":"\n- Arrive in : general location \n- Arrive at: specific location ","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"72","subcategorylv2":"4","type":"1"},{"question":"She ______ a lot of beer.","a":"drink","b":"drunk","c":"drinked","d":"drank","answer":"4","explain":"\n- Verb tense: Present (Present tense) - Past (Past tense)- Past Participle (Perfect tense) \n- Drink - Drank - Drunk","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"72","subcategorylv2":"4","type":"1"},{"question":"Have you ______ my new book?","a":"seed","b":"sawed","c":"seen","d":"seing","answer":"3","explain":"\n\n- Verb tense: Present (Present tense) - Past (Past tense)- Past Participle (Perfect tense)\n\n- See - Saw - Seen","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"72","subcategorylv2":"4","type":"1"},{"question":"The train has arrived ______ the station on time.","a":"on","b":"in","c":"at","d":"-","answer":"3","explain":"\n- Arrive in : general location \n- Arrive at: specific location ","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"72","subcategorylv2":"4","type":"1"},{"question":"Is that expensive?' 'I ______ ","a":"pay","b":"payed","c":"paid","d":"payd","answer":"3","explain":"\n\n- Verb tense: Present (Present tense) - Past (Past tense)- Past Participle (Perfect tense)\n\n- Pay - Paid - Paid","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"72","subcategorylv2":"4","type":"1"},{"question":"They have arrived ______ England today.","a":"on","b":"at","c":"in","d":"-","answer":"3","explain":"\n- Arrive in : general location \n- Arrive at: specific location ","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"72","subcategorylv2":"4","type":"1"},{"question":"She ______ me yesterday's newspaper.","a":"give","b":"gave","c":"given","d":"gived","answer":"2","explain":"\n\n- Verb tense: Present (Present tense) - Past (Past tense)- Past Participle (Perfect tense)\n\n- Give - Gave - Given","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"72","subcategorylv2":"4","type":"1"},{"question":"I ______ up at seven o'clock yesterday morning.","a":"wake","b":"waked","c":"waken","d":"woke","answer":"4","explain":"\n- Verb tense: Present (Present tense) - Past (Past tense)- Past Participle (Perfect tense) \n- Wake - Woke - Waken","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"72","subcategorylv2":"4","type":"1"},{"question":"Has she ______ for the new job?","a":"applied","b":"applyied","c":"applyed","d":"aplied","answer":"1","explain":"\n\n- Verb tense: Present (Present tense) - Past (Past tense)- Past Participle (Perfect tense)\n\n- Apply - Applied- Applied","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"72","subcategorylv2":"4","type":"1"}]}